

## SHIRONE FORTUNO

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

A passionate and dedicated Junior Software Engineer specializing in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Salesforce and Google Firebase with strong fundamentals in utilizing web development frameworks such as Tailwind and Bootstrap 5.

Have done several projects involving front and back end development.

**Q** 04-645-848-09

+63-995-718-2778

Shironebfortuno@gmail.com

in Shirone Fortuno

https://github.com/shironeF

4108, Tanza, Cavite.

web portfolio

## Education

# Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Cavite State University | 2012-2015 Undergraduate

## Reference

Mr. BRYL LIM.

Co-founder & CEO of PocketDevs

bryllim@gmail.com

## Work Experience

### **Customer Service Representative**

SOW Philippines Fulfillment Inc. (PAYO) | 2019 - 2021

- Implement effective strategies to optimize successful deliveries of PAYO's partner merchants products.
- Answer all emails and calls to address customer concerns and expectations.
- Develop a strong professional business relationship as a key point of contact for the company between merchants and their clients.

### **Customer Service Representative**

Call2Connect Solutions Inc. | 2016 - 2017

- Active engagement with clients in product launches and promotional campaigns
- Acquire new clients and increase business with existing customers.
- · Accelerate the growth of sales.

## Project Experience

### FoodPad v2 React, Tailwind, Google Firebase

### **Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp**

- Food ordering website.
- Using API, administrators can log in and upload new products using an admin account in real time.
- Customers can place, add and remove orders which exhibits accurate sum and total quantity of orders placed in the cart.

#### **Contributions**

- · Designing and Lavout.
- Database and API implementation.
- Log in system and User Authentication

### FoodPad v1 HTML, CSS, Javascript

#### Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

- Static Food delivery service website that demonstrate original designs and aesthetics.
- Users can navigate through different pages of the web that demonstrate how a food delivery service be like.

#### **Contributions**

- · Designing and Layout
- · HTML & CSS coding
- · Javascript implementation

## Skills

#### Front-end Back-end Database CRM

- HTML
- PHP
- MySQL
- Salesforce

CSS

- Firebase
- Javascript
- React